# ANNA MAMCHYCH

#### DATA ANALYTICS | DATA SCIENCE

- +48 690 493 749 | +38 099 026 15 68
- 🔀 annamamch17@gmail.com
  - Remote
- in linkedin.com/in/anna-mamchych
- https://annnamm.github.io/ [Portfolio]

### PROFILE

A creative and disciplined individual with a strong background in the arts, having graduated after seven years of study at an art school. I am passionate about continuous self-improvement, regularly attending industry conferences, seminars, and events related to the IT world. Outside of my professional interests, I enjoy strategic thinking through chess, as well as exploring the rich history of Ancient Egyptian mythology. I maintain an active lifestyle, regularly going to the gym, and bring a combination of creativity, problem-solving skills, and dedication to any project or team I am part of.

## WORK EXPERIENCE 🖻

#### **Teacher of English for children**

10.2023 - present Remote

 Conducted individual classes for children aged 5-17 years, led conversation clubs and activity clubs (drawing and Minecraft in English), also filled out reports and worksheets.

### **Trainee (IT department)**

06.2023 - 08.2023 PEPCO, Poznań

 Acquired knowledge of processing, transformation, interpretation and visualization of data. Gained experience with EXCEL and ERP. Learned how to use DAX. Practiced using Power BI.

# ACHIEVEMENTS &

### **New Technologies for Women - Ukraine**

09.2023 to 06.2024

Poland

• Laureate of the NTDD Ukraine grant program prize sponsored by Intel and Perspektywy.

## EDUCATION &

# The Adam Mickiewicz University of Poznan | 10.2024 - present

MSc in Mathematics and informatics: Data analysis and processing

# The Adam Mickiewicz University of Poznan | 10.2021 - 07.2024

BSc in Mathematics and informatics: Statistics and data analysis

Bsc thesis - Statistical analysis of the impact of the introduction of the "Safe Credit 2%" program on apartment prices in Poland.

# The Ivan Franko National University of Lviv | 09.2020 - 06.2024

BSc in Applied mathematics and informatics: System analysis and management. Data science

Thesis - Three-step method of minimizing a function in a basis gradient method.

Thesis - Three-step method of minimizing a function in a basis difference analogue of the Davidon-Fletcher-Powell method.

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

Soft

Flexibility of mind - Attention to details -Critical Thinking - Time Management -Knowledge principles of OOP

Hard

Python - R - PostgreSQL - MongoDB - Tableu - Office programs - HTML/CSS

#### LANGUAGES

- English above average
- Polish fluent
- Ukrainian fluent

#### CERTIFICATES

- EF SET English level C1
- NVIDIA Getting Started with Deep Learning
- Google Analytics for Beginners
- Google Analytics Advanced
- MongoDB (13 certificates)